Guide to the Sally Belfrage Papers TAM.189
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Correspondence, 1934-2000
  - Subseries II:B: Correspondence -- Alphabetical (Note: Closed until 2021), 1950-1994
    - Higgins, Doris, 1989-1993 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Hiss, Alger and Isabel, 1981-1993 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Hobson, Dave, 1980-1992 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Hochman-Leve, Sandra (a.k.a. Sandy Levinson), 1963-1972 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Holmes, Sally, 1959-1968 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Inglis, Brian, 1989-1992 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Ingrams, Michael, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Jackson, Derek, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Johnson, George ("GAJ"), 1964-1982 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - de Kay, Ormonde, 1985-1990 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Kershaw, Richard, 1959-1986 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Khan, Masud, 1960-1965, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Kinnell, Galway, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Koch, Chris, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Koningsberger, Hans (later Hans Koning), 1963-1965 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Kurnitz, Harry, 1960-1961 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Lampell, Millard ("Mill"), 1959-1961, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Lawder, Doug, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Lee, Dilsey (SB's childhood nanny), 1958-1964 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Leggett, Tim, 1987-1990 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Lindsay, Deacon, 1964-1989 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Lindsay, John V., 1964 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Lurie, Alison, 1982-1992 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Lynd, Staughton, 1965-1970, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - MacDowell Colony (Correspondence), 1964-1991 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - MacDowell Colony (Brochures, Literature), 1964-1985 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - MacDowell Colony (Notes, Articles, etc.), ca.1960-1990 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Maclean, Donald, ca.1950-1960 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Mahlau, Frank, 1958-1966 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Manheimer, Josh C., 1980-1993 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Marquand, John P. Jr. ("Johnny"), 1981 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Marquand, John P. Jr.; Jan-Mar, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Marquand, John P. Jr.; Apr-Jul, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Marquand, John P. Jr.; Sep-Dec, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Marquand, John P. Jr., 1983-1993 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Martin, H.L., 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Martinez, Eliabeth ("Betita"), 1969-1992 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - McKenzie, Alan ("Scotty"), 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Merritt, Anna, 1981-1991 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Michie, James, ca.1963-1969 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Mitford, Jessica ("Decca"), 1965, 1970-1977 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Mitford, Jessica, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Mitford, Jessica, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Mitford, Jessica, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Mitford, Jessica, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Mitford, Jessica (in SB's "Decca" Files, xeroxed unsigned letter), ca.1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Mitford, Jessica, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Mitford, Jessica, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Mitford, Jessica, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Mitford, Jessica CLOSED UNTIL 2021, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 10A)
    - Mitford, Jessica, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Mitford, Jessica, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Mitford, Jessica, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Mitford, Jessica, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Mitford, Jessica, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Mitford, Jessica, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Mitford, Jessica, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Mitford, Jessica, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Moor, Paul, 1982-1994 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Morera, Gabriel, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Mott, Stewart, 1965-1975 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Movarsky, Stefan, 1984-1993 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Muller, Ankie and Pi, 1974-1993 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Muncke, Ina (Iria?), 1988-1993 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Myers, Henry, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Nashishibi, Sari (SB's first Husband) (Correspondence and Divorce), 1960-1962 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Norman, Frank, ca.1958 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - O'Hehir, Diana, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Oxenhorn, Harvey; Sep-Oct 1983 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Oxenhorn, Harvey; Nov 1983-1990 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Palfi, Marion, 1964-1966 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Palmer, Jennifer (Re: a dissertation about Cedric Belfrage), 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - "Paula", ca.1980-1987 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Perutz, Kathy ("K"), 1961-1965 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Perutz, Kathy, 1968-1975 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Pilcher, Matti, 1964-1968 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Pirie, N. W. ("Bill"), 1959-1991 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Pluntze, Jack, 1987-1989 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Pozner, Vladimir ("Bill"), 1957-1991 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Ptashne, Mark, 1974-1977 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Rabin, Zell, 1959-1964 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Rath, Frederick ("Rick"), 1953-1958 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Robinson, John, 1957-1977 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Rosten, Norman, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Rowe, Newton A., 1958 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Rukeyser, Muriel, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Sacks, Oliver, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Salisbury, Harrison E., 1964-1984 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Sayre, Nora, 1970-1994 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Schafer, Mark, 1990-1992 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Schneider, Steve, 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Schneider, Steve, 1965-1985 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Shabib, Talib Hussein, 1960-1966, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Sharett, Kovi, 1963-1993 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Shawwaf, Ziad, 1960-1984 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Sillitoe, Ruth, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Simon, John, 1970-1991 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Smith, Clive and Socorro Bastida, 1978-1987 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Smith, Jay, 1958-1965 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Smith, Lorna, 1964-1967 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Sonnenberg, Benjamin, Jr., 1961-1962 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Sonnenberg, Benjamin, Jr., 1964-1976 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Sonnenberg, Benjamin, Jr., 1977-1992 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Starcke, Jessamin, 1977-1987 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Stewart, Don, Jr. ("Duck"), 1960, 1980-1981 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Sumner, Cid, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Sullivan, Patricia, 1989-1994 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Train, Arthur, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Train, Michael ("Mike," "Monk"), 1962 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Train, Michael, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Train, Michael, 1964-1976 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Train, Michael, 1976-1981 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Train, Michael, 1982-1990 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Train, Michael (Misc. Writings), ca.1970-1989 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Turkel, Studs, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Ture, Kwame (a.k.a. Stokeley Carmichael), 1986-1992 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Tweedie, Jill, 1970, 1980-1993 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Tynan, Elaine (nee Dundy) and Kenneth, 1961-1961, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Uieffer, Gerhard, 1958-1961 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Center for the Creative Arts, 1981, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Wandor, Michelene, ca.1978-1983 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Warner, Donald, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Weber, Palmer, 1953-1967 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Weber, Palmer, 1968-1986 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - West, Sophia; 1978-May 1980, 1978-1980 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - West, Sophia; Jun 1980-1994 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Williams, Claude, ca.1964 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Winter, Ella, 1975-1979 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Wiseman, Fred, 1980-1993 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - "Wladimir", 1958-1959 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Yang, Gladys, 1979-1982 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Yokum, Mike, 1979-1983 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Yurick, Sol, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Zaretsky, Eli, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Zatz, Asa, 1975-1991 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Subseries II:C: Correspondence -- Chronological (Note: Closed until 2021), 1947-2000
    - Correspondence, 1947, 1954-1959 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence (Undated); [c. 1959-1967], ca.1959-1967 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1960-1963 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence; Jan- Aug, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence; Sept-Dec, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, etc. (Undated), 1990-2000 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Undated correspondence to SB (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Series III: Writings, 1845-2000
  - Subseries III:A: Articles, Reviews, Fiction., 1959-1999
    - Writings about travels in Middle East (possibly a draft for a novel)., ca.1959-1960 (Box 23A, Folder 1)
    - "Assassination in Context" (article about the Middle East )., 1960 (Box 23A, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Personal Writings., ca.1960-1970 (Box 23A, Folder 3)
    - Poems., ca.1962, 1974 (Box 23A, Folder 4)
    - Reviews and Misc Brief Published Writings., 1964-1990 (Box 23A, Folder 5)
    - "The First Wife" (about Sari Nashashibi's death)., ca.1973 (Box 23A, Folder 6)
    - Reviews for Time Out., 1976-1977, 1981-1982 (Box 23A, Folder 7)
    - 2 Articles (by SB) about Children's TV and Sesame Street., ca.1977 (Box 23A, Folder 8)
    - Letters to The Observer complaining about SB's TV reviews., 1977 (Box 23A, Folder 9)
    - Notes, etc, relating to SB's TV reviews, 1977-1978 (Box 23A, Folder 10)
    - The Observer TV reviews (and drafts), 1977-1978 (Box 23A, Folder 11)
    - Proposal for TV series, with related items, ca.1980-1982 (Box 23A, Folder 12)
    - Article on Randolph Avenue, ca.1980-1985 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - "Being Seen" Story/Diary Excerpt, ca.1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - "Death Double Dealing" (notes on parents' deaths), 1987-1989 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Story fragment (?) about Sari Nashashibi, ca.1980-1999 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - "Fame" (notes for an article-?), ca.1990 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - "If the Cat Dies" - One-act play, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - "News" Short semi-autobiographical story, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Subseries III:B: Room in Moscow, 1845-1992
    - Letter from "Room in Moscow" files; 1845 (?), ca.1845 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - SB's ticket and train schedule to Moscow World Youth Festival, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Moscow Guidebook, ca.1950-1960 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Memorabilia from "Moscow and China" file, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Letters and memorabilia from 1957 trip to China, and from subsequent 1978 reunion trip, 1957, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Diary Excerpts by David Hollister (etc) from 1957 trip to China, 1957, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence and book contract, 1957-1959 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Outlines, ca.1958 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Notes and Odd inserts, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Rough Draft: Forward (Chapter One), 1958 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Rough Draft: Chapters Two -Four, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Rough Draft Chapters Five-Nine, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Rough Draft Chapters Ten-Fifteen, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Late Draft Chapters One-Seven, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Late Draft Chapters Eight-Fifteen, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Reviews and Publicity, 1958-1959 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Letters from readers, 1958-1966 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Series of Articles by SB about Moscow, in The Daily Mail, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence with Russians insisting SB is "anti-Soviet" (From Daily Mail articles), 1958 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Article about SB in Moscow- in Munchner (German magazine), 1958 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Excerpt of "A Room in Moscow" in Literary Cavalcade; Mar-1959 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence re: Mike Wallace interview with SB (transcript of interview in Box 37, folder 3), 1959 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Cosmopolitan article about SB, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Two travel articles on Russia (by SB?), ca.1959 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Burgess and MacLean: Article in Daily Telegraph Magazine - mentions SB, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Subseries III:C: Freedom Summer, 1952-1993
    - Notes on a scriptural basis for equal rights- by an Alabama preacher, ca.1952 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Drafts of two articles by SB about the South (Virginia, North Carolina, & Georgia), for the New Republic, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Article in the New Republic about Danville, Virginia, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Article in The National Guardian about Claude Williams, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Three-ring binder "Notes: Freedom Summer", 1964-1965 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Draft: Short fragments and notes, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Draft: Chapters one and two, 1964-1965 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Draft: Pieces of chapters three- five, 1964-1965 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Draft: Chapters six-ten, 1964-1965 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Draft: Chapters eleven-fifteen, 1964-1965 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Medical Committee for Human Rights: "Manual for Southern Medical Projects Presence- Program for Civil Rights movement", 1965 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Reviews and Publicity, ca.1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Letters from readers, 1965-1967, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence with Viking Press and Andre Deutsch, 1965-1968 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Article for Fact Magazine about Scottsboro Boys, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Excerpt in The Insurgent (W. E. B. Dubois Clubs' magazine) and correspondence with Viking, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - 3-Part article by SB ("Cry Freedom") in Women's Mirror (copies), 1966 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - 3-Part article by SB ("Cry Freedom") in Women's Mirror (original), 1966 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Japanese edition: Correspondence with translator, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Notes and Articles on Civil Rights Movement, Race in US, etc, ca.1980-1990 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Three Lectures on Civil Rights Movement- by Julian Bond, John Dittmer, and unknown, ca.1980-1990 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Two articles on Women and the Civil Rights Movement (re: Virginia Durr and Johnnie Carr), 1980-1990 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Essay on Cora Tucker and Civil Rights by Elizabeth Jones, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Lecture on Civil Rights Movement by Anne Braden, ca.1988 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Essay on Women and Civil Rights Movement by Sandra Cason (a.k.a. Casey Hayden), 1989 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Lecture by SB on Women and the Civil Rights Movement, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Essay on Movement History by Martha Norman, ca.1990 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - "The Civil Rights Movement: A Symposium": SB's Notes and Lecture, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - "The Civil Rights Movement: A Symposium": Correspondence and Program, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Bookworld: "Freedom Summer" M. Krauss, 1965 August 10 (Box 43, Reel 1)
  - Subseries III:D: Flowers of Emptiness, 1933-1985
    - Manuscript, ca.1979 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Drafts for afterward, including letters, and Rajneesh transcripts, 1970-1980 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Afterward, ca.1980 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence with friends in Poona, memorabilia from India, 1976-1979 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Notebooks and Loose Notes, 1976-1980 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence with Rajneesh Foundation re: pamphlets, copyrights, 1977-1982 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Transcripts of Rajneesh, drafts of paraphrased Rajneesh, 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence with Publishers, reviews, publicity, and covers, 1979-1981 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence with readers; March-Sept 1981 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence with readers; Oct 1981-Feb 1982, 1981-1982 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence with readers; March 1982-1985 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Agostini, Lewis: Correspondence re: Guru Meher Baba, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Brownell, Fred: Correspondence, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Two articles about Rajneesh (From The New Yorker, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Pirie, Bill: Articles (etc), 1933-1979 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Information on schools and food programs in India; mid 1970's, 1972-1978 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - SB's notes, on Leaf Protein project in India and Bill Pirie; mid 1970's, 1972-1978 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Subseries III:E: The Crack, 1980-1991
    - Early notes and clippings (at the time called, "Women and War"), ca.1984 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Notes and Notebooks on Northern Ireland, ca.1984-1987 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Notes on Language in Belfast, etc., ca.1984-1987 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Notes, etc from folder "Add to Final Version", ca.1985 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Notes, etc, "For additional chapter 'Quigley and Kavanagh'", ca.1985 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous notes on Northern Ireland, ca.1984-1987 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Initial Draft-- assorted pages, ca.1986 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Misc. Drafts for sections of The Crack, ca.1986 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Misc. Drafts for sections of The Crack, ca.1986 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Odds and Ends for early draft, ca.1986 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Notes, etc. for Chapter one, ca.1986 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Draft- Chapter one (and intro), 1986 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Notes, etc. for Chapter two, ca.1986 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - "The Crack:" Draft- Chapter two, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Notes, etc. for Chapter three, ca.1986 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Draft- Chapter three, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Notes, etc. for Chapter four, ca.1986 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Draft- Chapter four, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Notes, etc. for Chapter five, ca.1986 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Draft- Chapter five, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Notes, etc. for Chapter six, ca.1986 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Draft-- Chapter six, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Notes, etc. for Chapter seven, ca.1986 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Draft- Chapter seven, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Notes, etc. for chapter eight, ca.1986 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Draft- Chapter eight, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Notes, etc. for Chapter nine, ca.1986 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Draft- Chapter nine, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Notes, etc. for Chapter ten, ca.1986 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Draft- Chapter ten, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Notes, etc for. Chapter eleven, ca.1986 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Draft- Chapter eleven, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Notes, etc. for Chapter twelve, ca.1986 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Draft- Chapter twelve, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Notes, etc. for Chapter thirteen, ca.1986 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Draft- Chapter thirteen, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Notes, etc. from folder "End", ca.1986 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Draft- Chapters fourteen - sixteen, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Fennell, Desmond: Correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Hall, Michael: 2 plays about Belfast, "Expecting the Future" and "Missing from the Future", 1983, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Hall, Michael: Correspondence, etc., 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Lyons, Dr. H. A.: Correspondence, etc., 1986 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - McAteer, Michael: Poems, ca.1985 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Murphy, John A: Correspondence, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Publicity, incl Interview with SB in The Guardian, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Covers, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Reviews, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Letters From Readers, 1987-1990 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Short Pieces about N. Ireland, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Two Articles by SB in The Nation, 1987, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence with The Nation, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - BBC Script based on The Crack (Draft w/ edits by SB), 1988 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Screenplay (Scenes 1-52), 1988 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Screenplay(Scenes 53-End), 1988 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Notes on interview transcripts, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Subseries III:F: Transcript Folders/ by name., 1980-1990
    - Ardill, Austin and Molly, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Attwood, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Bennett, Eithne, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Berkery, Moira, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - "Bernie and Mary", ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Bingham, Dora, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Bingham, John, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Campion, June, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Cousins, Margaret, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Devin, Paddy, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Dorrian, Michelle, and Moira Berkery, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - "Dunlop", ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Dunn, Hester ("Hester at the Switchboard"), ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Edgerton, Lynda, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Elliott, Dorothy, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Emery, Betty, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Evason, Eileen, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Feenan, Kathleen, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Feeney, Brian, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Fennell, Desmond, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - "Ferguson", ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - "Gerry"- with Brenda and Keenan, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Greer, Stephen, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Groves, Emma, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Groves, Liz, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Hall, Michael, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - "Jack", ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Jordan, Winnie, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Kelly, Kate, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - "Louis", ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Lunn, Peter, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Martin, Francis, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - McAteer, Maggie, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - McAuley, Chrissy, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - McCormack, Inez, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - McDermott, Eilish, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 41)
    - "Meehan", ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 42)
    - Molloy, Chrissy and Paddy, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 43)
    - Mulholland, Marie, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 44)
    - Murphy, Pauline, ca.1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 45)
    - Murray, Frances and Lily, ca.1980-1990 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Newell, Caroline, ca.1980-1990 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Nolan, Mark, ca.1980-1990 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Paisley, Ian, ca.1980-1990 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Power, Margaret, ca.1980-1990 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - "Protestants Protest", ca.1980-1990 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Quiery, Marie, ca.1980-1990 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Reid, 'Fr', ca.1980-1990 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Rice, Betty, ca.1980-1990 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Rice, Mrs. Jane, and Joyce McCarten, ca.1980-1990 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Robb, John, ca.1980-1990 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Short, Paddy, ca.1980-1990 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - "Simon", ca.1980-1990 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Sloane, Victor, ca.1980-1990 (Box 31, Folder 14)